animecharactersdatabase.com 2016-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Anime Characters Database

#### 3rd Party Ads Privacy Policies

#### Opt Out

You can disable 3rd Party content server side by using the button below. This will tell our web server to stop including Ad code in web pages. You may also want to remove any cookies set by 3rd party sites as well. 

As a fan of [tosdr](https://tosdr.org/) here is a summary of our Terms of Service in their style.

    + Pseudonym allowed
    + Only the necessary logs and debug information are kept
    + Anime Characters Database warns you if emergency maintenance is happening
    
    - Terms may be changed any time at their discretion, without notice to the user
    - Anime Characters Database can use your content for all their existing and future services
    - Anime Characters Database may stop providing services to you at any time
    - Your account can be suspended and your data deleted any time for any reason
    - You shall defend and indemnify Anime Characters Database
    - Anime Characters Database uses temporary session cookies
    
    × You cannot delete your account
    × We can remove your content at any time and without prior notice
    × Deleted images are not really deleted

## email address

    We require a valid email address for account registration and verification.
    We will send you one email at the time of registration.
    We will not send you emails without your permission.
     - You can enable PM notifications by email.
     - You can also enable email notification on the who's this character board.
     - You can request a password reset be sent to your email.
    We will not sell your email address.

## passwords

    Passwords are stored in an encrypted format.
    Only one administrator has access to changing passwords.

## any additional personal information you choose to provide

    We operate under the expectation that all information you provide is false, and inaccurate.
    
    ACDB is not in the business of profiling or data-mining.
    Any opportunities to provide personal details will always allow for creative responses.
    For example, when we ask for your age, you can enter anything from 0 to 9999. 
     Immortals are totally welcome here!
    We also provide many joke options when it comes to gender.
    ACDB believes in the old-skool spirit of anonymity and fun.

## Wed Sep 16 11:55:21 CDT 2015

    Added a TOSDR style review of some of our worst policies.
    Presently we use Google Analytics, Google Ads, sovrn ads, and any of their partners. 

## Update: Fri Sep 26 21:09:37 CDT 2014

    We are now working with Q1 Media and Google AdSense as our primary ad providers.
    Google Analytics has been re-enabled.
    
    Added updated links to 3rd Party Privacy Policies

## Update: Fri Aug 24 09:41:22 CDT 2012

    We are now working with Lijit Networks, Inc.
    
    Added updated links to 3rd Party Privacy Policies

## Update: Sat Jul 14 23:14:17 CDT 2012

    We now include Quantcast tracking code, but ONLY on this page ( privacy.php ). 
    However, our 3rd party ads often will use Quantcast on other parts of the site. 

##  Update: Sat Mar 31 05:36:16 CDT 2012 

    We no longer use Google AdSense.
    
    We now use PulsePoint ads.
    
    We have implemented a login accounting system.
    Each time you login or logout of Anime Characters Database
    we record:
     - the time
     - your ip
     - the User Agent your web browser sent in the http headers
     - user name
     - user id
     - session id
    
    This information is only available to L10 admins.
    This information is to be used only for investigating suspicious account activity. 

## Updated: May 15th, 2011

    Time for a new Privacy Policy.
    
    Change Number 1: We no long use Google Analytics Tracking services.
    
    We do our best to balance the need for Ad Revenue and respecting your privacy.
    
    All members have the option to Turn Off Ads by clicking a button in the side menu.
    Anyone can visit the Privacy Policy and click a similar button within the page.
    
    We try to minimize the amount of 3rd party content on the site.
    I can't stand web sites that connect to hundreds of third party sources,
     so I wont force that on the users of my web site.
    Where there are member comments, you may encounter 3rd party hosted Avatars,
     or linked images in comments.
    
    Anime Characters Database can be fully used with JavaScript turned off,
     and works great with NoScript ( a firefox extension ).
    Such a choice will make us worry about paying our hosting bills,
     but offers you faster browsing speeds, and max privacy!
    
    We do collect standard web access logs.
    These contain:
     - IP address
     - request time
     - request type
     - request URL
     - referrer URL
     - user agent
     - transfer size
     - status code
    We keep these logs for roughly a year.
    We do not sell our access logs.
    We do not share entire logs with anyone.
    Sections of logs may be made public.
    
    Our database at most records:
     - IP address
     - user agent
     - time
    as identifying markers when you post content to the site.
    The purpose being to identify spammers, and quickly remove related spam.
    
    We also maintain a usage stats table, which contains:
     - time first seen
     - time last seen
     - page requests
     - online today marker
     - ip address
     - session cookie
     - user agent
    Purpose: 
     - maintain a reliable user session
     - detect and prevent Denial of Service attacks
    
    Members are free to submit as much or as little personal information in their
     account profiles. 
    We try hard to maintain an unusually high level of server security.
    While we do have substantial security preventing intrusion, we have also
     spent vast amounts of time and effort obscuring the internals of our system
     to a point that should a hacker gain access, they will have a very foreign, 
     very limited system opened to them.

|  

Member Benefits

**No ads for members!** Enjoy acdb ad free by registering and logging in today. What are you waiting for? It's easy! Begin your epic adventure. Find treasure, collect cards, hoard jewels, become an **Epic Member**

|   
---|---|---  
  
### Character of the

### Day

| 

### Week

| 

### Month  
  
---|---|---  
 |   |    
  
###  VS 

_superwarioman asks_ **Who is better**  
 _wins the funniest girls_

Ayumu Kasuga

Nano Shinonome

New VS

###  View More VS Matches

| 

### LATEST FORUM POSTS

Re:Who is this character/what anime??
[quote1465660510=AmaterasuWings] Pretty sure it&#[more ...]
    Sun 6:18 AM | Hairyguy4
Re:Who is this character/what anime??
Pretty sure it's [urll=source.php?id=104051]B[more ...]
    Sat 11:55 AM | AmaterasuWings
Who is this character/what anime??
Found this and am wracking my brains trying to fig[more ...]
    Fri 4:44 PM | Hairyguy4

### More Forum Posts

| 

### GUILD ACTIVITY TODAY

 Worshipers of Celestine Lucullus
    Rank #1

###  _Activity Points_

| 

###  GUILD COIN WARS 

 Celestine Lucullus
    Worshipers of Celestine Lucullus bid  2 coins on Jun 7, 2016
 Ohana Matsumae
    The Color Cafe bid  1 coin on Jun 4, 2016
 Umi Kouzaki
    The Color Cafe bid  1 coin on Jun 4, 2016
 Ui Nakatsugawa
    The Color Cafe bid  1 coin on Jun 4, 2016
 Kongou
    The Color Cafe bid  1 coin on Jun 4, 2016

### View More  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
### New Short Characters Comments

|   | DakuNekoNyaa | 12:48 pm  
---|---|---  
  
ALL HAIL GOD ALL HAIL GOD  
  
### New Short Anime and Games Comments

|    | Rei | Jun 10, 2016  
---|---|---  
  
Short episodes, over powered bikinis!  
  
### Reviews

| 7  | Gangsta | Feb 24, 2016 / Feb 24, 2016 | by AmaterasuWings | Review length: Long  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
### Trending

female anime characters   
black anime characters   
male anime characters   
best anime characters   
kawaii anime characters

### Chatbox

12:13 pm  
<DakuNekoNyaa> I don't mind it 

Yesterday 11:46 pm  
<Lucy_Heartfilia>

Jun 10, 2016  
<Aoi-chan ")> I love Hetalia!^^ 

Jun 9, 2016  
<Rei> I haven't watched it. 

Jun 8, 2016  
<TeddyBear13> Anyone here like Hetalia? 

Jun 1, 2016  
<Rei> You can turn it off in My Account

May 31, 2016  
<will1by2> How to turn off filter 

May 23, 2016  
<Rei> ^_^ 

May 23, 2016  
<Drago530> 😁😁😁😁 

May 2, 2016  
<Rei> Who Board thread listing now includes latest reply info. Thanks to Nuit for the idea. ^_^ 

* * *

  * Chatbox History

* * *  
  
### Who's This Character Board

08:32 pm

|  Anonymous | 

Replies: 1  
  
---|---|---  
Who is this ?  |  [](https://i.gyazo.com/bed9e59c3aabe9fa89afc146cf55a6d8.png) **PNG**  
  
08:00 pm

|  Anonymous | 

Replies: 1  
  
---|---|---  
Who is this ?  |  [](http://i.imgur.com/xN8lqE9.gif) **GIF**  
  
05:57 pm

|  Anonymous | 

Replies: 1  
  
---|---|---  
Who is this ?  |  [](http://moe.animecharactersdatabase.com/uploads/who/36662-1793167358.jpg) NSFW (18+) **JPG**  
  
## [[ View MORE ]](https://web.archive.org/web/20160613025039id_/http%3A//www.animecharactersdatabase.com/who.php)

URL |   
---|---  
Comment |   
Name |   
NSFW (18+) ?   
  
Post a link to an image you want the Anime Characters Database Community to Identify

|  

Member Benefits

**No ads for members!** Enjoy acdb ad free by registering and logging in today. What are you waiting for? It's easy! Begin your epic adventure. Find treasure, collect cards, hoard jewels, become an **Epic Member**

|   
---|---|---  
  
###  Donate 

0 $ |  | 109 $  
---|---|---  
  
Raised this month: 0 $ (0%)

Current Goal: Keep ACDB ad free for members.

Supporters

  *    
A-Z Characters
  *    
A-Z Series
  *    
character
  *    
Anime
  *    
Calendar
  *    
Forum
  *    
Image Board
  *    
Guilds
  *    
Latest
  *    
Music DB
  *    
News
  *    
Seasons
  *    
Tags
  *    
Who
